{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Skylight Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40152/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40152,"taskName":"Skylight - Install","taskDescription":"Install a New Skylight","xmTaskDescriptor":"Skylight Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":296,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Skylight custom skylsights roof tubular","textMessagingName":"Install Skylight","rolloverLongDesc":"This category is for firms that cut through the roof, install the skylight \u0026 finish off the exterior \u0026 interior openings. It includes light tunnels \u0026 solar tubes that carry natural daylight longer distances, as well roof windows that form their own through-the-roof balconies. Note separate category for repairing or replacing an existing skylight.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes solar tubes \u0026 roof windows.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a New Skylight.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Skylight Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace or Install Skylight Window","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":71,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Skylight Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Skylight - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Skylight Project","urlName":"Skylight-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Skylight Installation Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Skylight,custom,skylsights,roof,tubular,skyligt,,skylights","emcCategoryOid":-12066,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":462,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40152/":{"taskOID":40152,"originalTaskOID":40152,"setID":462,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1105,"questionDisplayText":"Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description of what you need.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3131,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I need to purchase skylight(s)","answerDisplayText":"I need to purchase skylight(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3129,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I need a contractor to install skylight(s) in an existing opening","answerDisplayText":"I need a contractor to install skylight(s) in an existing opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3128,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"I need a contractor to cut an opening in an existing roof, reframe, and install skylight(s)","answerDisplayText":"I need a contractor to cut an opening in an existing roof, reframe, and install skylight(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5626,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Roof","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of roof do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":866,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Asphalt shingle","answerDisplayText":"Asphalt shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7087,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood shake or shingle","answerDisplayText":"Wood shake or shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6464,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Traditional tile","answerDisplayText":"Traditional tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3609,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Lightweight tile","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3823,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Metal roof","answerDisplayText":"Metal roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6259,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tar \u0026 gravel, single ply or sprayed foam","answerDisplayText":"Tar \u0026 gravel, single ply or sprayed foam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1105,"questionDisplayText":"Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description of what you need.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3131,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I need to purchase skylight(s)","answerDisplayText":"I need to purchase skylight(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3129,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I need a contractor to install skylight(s) in an existing opening","answerDisplayText":"I need a contractor to install skylight(s) in an existing opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3128,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"I need a contractor to cut an opening in an existing roof, reframe, and install skylight(s)","answerDisplayText":"I need a contractor to cut an opening in an existing roof, reframe, and install skylight(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3131,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I need to purchase skylight(s)","answerDisplayText":"I need to purchase skylight(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3129,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I need a contractor to install skylight(s) in an existing opening","answerDisplayText":"I need a contractor to install skylight(s) in an existing opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3128,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"I need a contractor to cut an opening in an existing roof, reframe, and install skylight(s)","answerDisplayText":"I need a contractor to cut an opening in an existing roof, reframe, and install skylight(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5626,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Roof","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of roof do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":866,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Asphalt shingle","answerDisplayText":"Asphalt shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7087,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood shake or shingle","answerDisplayText":"Wood shake or shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6464,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Traditional tile","answerDisplayText":"Traditional tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3609,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Lightweight tile","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3823,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Metal roof","answerDisplayText":"Metal roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6259,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tar \u0026 gravel, single ply or sprayed foam","answerDisplayText":"Tar \u0026 gravel, single ply or sprayed foam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":866,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Asphalt shingle","answerDisplayText":"Asphalt shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7087,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood shake or shingle","answerDisplayText":"Wood shake or shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6464,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Traditional tile","answerDisplayText":"Traditional tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3609,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Lightweight tile","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3823,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Metal roof","answerDisplayText":"Metal roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6259,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tar \u0026 gravel, single ply or sprayed foam","answerDisplayText":"Tar \u0026 gravel, single ply or sprayed foam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}